foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
great
alhamdulillah
will
link up with the hot bus that Dean
Mahone has been giving us
and before I start I would like to draw
your attention to something that will
probably take for granted
and that is
here's the mosque that Advocates the
worship of Allah alone
I know that God sent Moses to preach as
we know in Surah 21.
and not to preach the glorification of
Moses
and God sent Jesus to preach the worship
of God alone
and not to preach the glorification of
Jesus
and God sent Muhammad to preach the
worship of God Alone
and not to preach the glorification of
Muhammad or anyone else
just worshiping God Alone
and this Mass we Advocate the worship of
God Alone
and we follow the Quran to the letter
we came to call this mosque the
University of God
because it is the most important
education and we have been very
fortunate in seeing the truth of the
Quran and sticking to every letter of it
the University of God the most important
education
black
official professorship
so you can see it from God's vantage
point he said well these people are
advocating the worship of me alone God
Alone
and they need the professor
so let's send them a profession
so God appoints a couple of angels to go
and hunt for the best Professor on Earth
and he gets us not only a professor but
a dean of the Islamic Institute in the
Philippines
no he doesn't know why
thank you
all he knows is set down he got stuck to
the message
and he's teaching us
this is her and he's been teaching us
about Adam and Eve and the sin of Adam
and Eve
and we've been enjoying his teaching so
we we have an official
not just any Professor the dean himself
off
foreign
that's what they did and because the
Earth from the tree
they do not qualify to continue in
Jannah in heaven however the kingdom of
God
because they ate through the tree
they committed one sin
what does this teach us what do we learn
from this important lesson we learn that
you cannot go to Jannah with one sin
if you have one sin then you record you
do not qualify to go to hell
sounds difficult but for the people who
worship Allah alone it is not difficult
at all because there are two ways of
wiping out the sins from your record
and this means nobody would see them you
will not see them in the record
if you fulfill these two requirements
but the thing we must learn
from then
Adams and Eve sin is the Earth from the
tree they were kicked out
because they committed one sin therefore
we learn from this that we cannot go to
heaven with one sin on our record not
one
if you commit one sin and you have it in
your record then you die you cannot go
to heaven
you must be absolutely sinless because
when Adam and Eve air from the tree
didn't commit murder then they ate from
the tree that's all they did God taught
them you go in heaven and hear it from
anything you want but not just one tree
the air from the tree and they were
kicked out
and this is exactly what we're doing
here on this Earth
we are here to be tested
and
to end this life without a sacred sin a
new record otherwise you do not qualify
to join the kingdom of God you do not
qualify to enter Germany
now how do we
what are the ways of erasing send from
your record
now this is one thing you must remember
you must never must never forget that
our goal is to end this life without the
sink of sin
how can we do that
the first method of erasing sin is told
repentance that's one thing
you turn to God and you say I'm sorry I
made a mistake I will never do it again
I pledge I will never do it again I
repent
I I I'm sorry I apologize
foreign
ly that you will not do it again
that's one way
what if your repentance is not
acceptable
there comes the second way the second
way to pay for it
the first right to arrest since is talba
repentance and the second one is to pray
for them here in this world
and they are very expensive I'm telling
you
I would like to to put
and another value on the sins and how
you pay for them here in this world now
as a Believer you will pay in material
things thank God you're not pay with
your arm and your legs or just look
around this mask you don't see anyone
with one arm away alhamdulillah
you have to say alhamdulillah every time
but
you would when I put material values in
it it seems like the punishment is out
of proportion for the sin
but you have to pay for it unless you
wanna you order the new record if you
want to watch you have one sin on your
record
you cannot go to Germany
people go and
commit adultery
and they think it's a simple matter
when marriage is really doesn't matter
if you have a relationship with another
person you might as well want to suggest
marriage
very simply two witnesses you before
Allah
you declare that you're married
but if you fall into adultery
my daughter value on it is ten thousand
dollars
you have to pay
in misery or if you don't have the ten
thousand dollars to be in problem
the payment percents
seems to be out of proportion in this
world but really it isn't it's a
tremendous mercy so the Believers are
the only people who enjoy
certain problems in this world because
they know they are paying for certain
wiping out certain sins
the believer
does not get away with sins in this
world he has to pay for it
the disbeliever doesn't either except
with the disbeliever the punishment
continues in the hereafter
with the disbeliever the punishment in
this world it also comes in this world
but he or she cannot make the connection
they will appear to get away with sin
and then after years months after a time
where the person cannot connect the
punishment to the sin then
they get hit
so the two ways
to erase sins
are repentance
and paying for them this is the only two
way
there's one sin not sin it's not even a
saint there's one offense that cannot be
forgive the only unforgivable offense I
will let you open the Quran now reach
for your Quran and get Surah 39 verse
53.
no excuse me I made a mistake 4 48.
not even that 417.
417 is Page 53.
all right this is the order God wants us
to see
this is not the one that I wanted to do
but it deals with repentance there's 53
verse 16 says
repentance is accepted by God from those
who fought and sent due to ignorance
then repent immediately
God redeems this and God is nowhere wise
so this is how repentance repentance is
accepted just go on but repentance is
not acceptable from those who continue
to commit sins until death comes to them
then say now I repent
nor is it acceptable from those who die
as disbelievers we have prepared for
this eventful distribution so repentance
there are conditions for accepting or
accepting repentance that you fall and
sin due to ignorance
otherwise you don't know that wine is
Haram
and you go and drink wine then you will
find out the Quran that's why
liquor alcohol is Haram
then you repent
and you bless you never do it again you
made a mistake you never do it again
then your repentance accept it but if
you know that's why liquor whiskey
marijuana or any of those is Haram and
you go to Liberty and you do it you
cannot repent from that you have to pay
and the price is very hard either heal
here or there
committed
you cannot repeat from there there's no
repentance there you have to pay
and the pay is very expensive ten
thousand dollars you know the
prostitutes a dollar for fifty dollars
but uh the price that you pay
according to God's law
is I put the paper in it just roughly
ten thousand dollars
in misery or problems or what else
so this is the condition for repentance
you can repent only if you fall into sin
due to ignorance and they repent
immediately
you can't linger
you know right away say I'm sorry God I
made a mistake
that's that's these are the conditions
for repentance
Also let's go to 3965.
because when I say you cannot go to
heaven with one sin it sounds terrible
doesn't it
not one sin because
committed one sin 39
60 party
Zuma
of the day
three one nine that's three one nine
verse number is 65.
no that's not the one
excuse me it's in the same page anyway
you say to my servants who exceeded the
limits never despair of God's mercy God
forgives all sins
for he is the forgiver the merciful
now the Arabic is even a lot stronger
all sins God forgives all sins
Moses committed murder
but he was forgiven
if you remember the Quran Moses
immediately turned to God and said this
is the act of the devil please God
forgive me he repented immediately
didn't he and he didn't intend to kiss
the man either
but he was forgiven right there in the
same breath
the same verse of the Quran so God
forgive forgive all sins
the instruction here for us is never to
despair from God's mercy
there is one unforgivable offense now
that's the one in 448.
let's go to four
sorry 48.
down at the bottom of the bottom of the
page
it says I got worship the only
unforgivable offense
God never forgives the idolization of
anything besides him and he forgives all
lesser offensions
for whomever he Wills
anyone who sets up any Idol besides God
and supports the growth blessing
therefore the only unforgivable offense
is idol worship and this is why you are
very careful in this Mass not to idolize
anyone not marrying not Jesus not
Muhammad not Moses not any not any saint
not anyone not anything
our motto is Allah alone
and the Criterion is in the Quran
when you talk about God I don't they
don't like it
that's the sign but we love it we talk
about Allah
because either worship is the only
unforgivable offense
that's about in the same
the same Surah verse 116 116.
stage 63
again at the bottom of the page
says guard does not forgive the
idolization of any Idols besides him
and he forgives all lesser offenses for
whomever he Wills
anyone who idolizes any Idol besides God
has gone for Australia
so now we know that there's only one
unforgivable offense that is either
worth it to idolize anyone or anything
because the one that does not forgiven
because the whole idea of creating Us in
this world
is to worship Allah alone
and this is why we are taught throughout
Quran that the prophets have no power to
benefit you or harm you have no power to
benefit themselves or harm themselves
why is God saying that
why because the people have tendency to
idolize the leaders their Saints their
Prophets
Christians idolize Jesus the Muslims
idolize Muhammad
the Shia idolize the imams
the plague the planet that Satan set up
for the Jews the Christians and the
Muslims and people thought in it
and we finally reflected in the Quran a
statement of fact
the majority of Believers fallen out of
the worship
the majority of people are not believe
to start with and the majority of the
minority will fall in idle worship
that's why you must be absolutely
positive and careful that you are
idolizing no one that you are worshiping
Allah alone that through the following
the Quran Allah
the words of Allah alone
you don't accept any instructions from
anyone because God is the wisest
so with this in mind
we know that all sins are forgivable
the only unforgivable offense is idol
worship
and we know that we cannot go to heaven
with one sin we must erase all
sins
otherwise
you don't go to heaven
we are here in this world to prepare for
entering Heaven that's what we want the
real life the eternal life
because this life is zero
so in order to qualify you have to
address all the sins you can arrest by
tauba repentance
and by impairing for them
therefore I I propose that to go out of
these doors absolutely sinless
we're gonna walk out of these doors
without the sink and sin on our record
because we're going to repent right now
we're going to turn to God and we're
going to declared Toba when I pledge
that we will never break God's law that
we will follow
his Commandments as stated here
and that will never
offense God in any way
either worship this out of the quest
we did that long time ago
but we're going to turn to God and
sincerely pledge we're going to repent
of all the past sins and offenses
we're gonna say that we're sorry that we
fell into those mistakes
will apologize
and we will pledge this is most
important that we will never again
commit a central
you have to mean it
you may fall in sin again which you will
but God says in the Quran that he loved
Allah
those who continuously repent didn't say
because you continue to repent you have
to repent every day but as far as we're
concerned at this moment we're going to
walk out of this doors absolutely
sinless
so thanks to God and repent to Allah
alhamdulillah
when you repent
if you wipe out all the sins new records
and you qualify
to go to hell if you die right now at
this moment you've got to have stretch
because you don't have a sanity wrap
and remember the conditions for
repentance
in the future when you reach for a cup
of whiskey or wine or something you know
it feels wrong and you know you're gonna
pay for it dearly it's very expensive
I remember one time and I I wasn't Lydia
at the time and
I was buying Donuts from this fellow and
he had a bottle of whiskey next to him
he was a cashier and he was black in a
way and I said you know it was very
expensive he said yeah I could add
barrels for this
if I said no that's not what I mean
it's gonna cost you a lot
because it's very expensive you're
breaking God's law as far as Adam and
Eve is concerned
the custom heaven
Heaven is a cut glass you do anything
you want God says you'll get anything
you wish and I have more
I have more than you wish
because God has things that we cannot
even imagine in order to wish you know
how can you wish for something cannot
imagine blessings and joy that you
cannot imagine
God says well the thy name is I have
more than what you wish for
and now that your sinless try to
maintain this condition
you're about to commit the sin
be prepared to pay for it deeply
expensively
you know what is worse with sins
is if they really if it really become
too much then they there's
a sheet that builds up with every sin
and if there's too much of that around
you people cannot penetrate that she
but never despair from God's mercy
you must repent immediately whether you
know it or not if you fall in sin
knowingly or unknowingly repent anyway
immediately
and be prepared for the price
and you pay the price happily
anytime God says you shall not
you shall not
no matter how simple it seems
the second husband is about the
importance of the Arabic language
this is the second book
because we started a lot of language
lessons recently
and I'm going to summarize those book by
one word
let me make it two words not important
at all that's four words not important
Arabic is not important at all because
we learn from Surah 41
let's look at 4144
you most of you are familiar with this
51 44
page three three two
so how do we had we made it a non-arabic
Quran they would have said why did it
come down in that language
whether it is not Arabic or Arabic say
for those who believe it is and the
healing regardless of the language
as for those who do not believe there
would be deaf and blind to it as if they
are being called from a past
so language is absolutely immaterial if
you're a Believer you're a sincere
Muslim then God would put everything in
your heart the whole Quran in your heart
I've seen people quote the Quran without
ever reading it because the sincere
Muslims they haven't read it all yet
they're working on it
at the same time if you're a professor
of Arabic Linguistics at the
Mecca University or whatever and you are
not a sincere believer you cannot get
one Arabic word from the Quran even
though you're the professor of Arabic
language
because most of God says so as for those
who do not believe they'll be blind to
it
we cannot get one word out of this at
the same time he's Japanese a French
sweep
or one who does not know one letter in
the Arabic language rather put the Quran
in his heart otherwise do not be fair
because the Quran is for the whole world
for everybody and it will not be fair
to restrict it to those who can lead the
right Arabic
as you see from this verse the title of
the Surah is
God made the Quran available to every
believer
and also the Quran is very special the
Quran is never available to those who
are not believable
people who do not believe the Quran but
the Arabic
the Arabic helps
just like mathematics or physics or
chemistry it helps
and that's why we have the Arabic
lessons I'm going to give you one
example where the Arabic helps
I wrote it out there
because the the Muslim ummah is trapped
in the
in a satanic what where they cannot be
do not believe God when he says that the
Quran is complete and perfect we have to
go to other sources they have five
sources of sharia
they have the Quran the Hadith is
that this energy and all kinds of other
sources and God says if you go to any
other source beside Quran
you are setting up a god besides God
read the verse for you it happens to be
verse 19 and 4 6. what are you saying
that follows ahead for the death is
foreign
other gods beside God
against the will of God and the will of
the prophet
and they think that they're like
one perfect example of the Arabic
language is this verse here
it says it's it's a Surah 17 verse 45 it
says when you read the Quran who plays
between you and those who do not believe
in the hereafter
an invisible barrier
and we bought
shields on their heart to prevent them
from understanding Quran and deafness in
their ears and when you mention your
lord when you preach your lord in the
Quran alone
God put the water alone after Quran
they turn away they run they don't like
it they run
and do we have seen this we have seen
people who will come here and you tell
them the Quran alone and they run
now because of the general
foreign
you just pick up any translation of the
Quran
and you will find that they they move
the world after you alone and that's why
in our translation after you you Lord
and after the Quran because God put it
after the Quran
this sentence would have been perfectly
perfectly perfect if you say
but God delivers before the world watch
the roof after the Quran so if you know
Arabic
it will help you
distinguish and understand that the
majority of people are plagued with idol
worship
and they are they are playing to the
extent that they refuse to believe the
Quran
they refused to translate the truth of
the Quran
if they cannot stand when you say Quran
alone God is not enough for them
and
chaos and his man and all these other
sources that were invented centuries
after the prophet including the Hadith
so this is an example of the importance
of the Arabic language
and why it here
the expression
and those who do not believe in the
Hereafter let's look at them
consistently
in the Quran you find first first of all
Surah 16 verse 22.
16 22.
[Applause]
1622 says your God is one God
but those who do not believe in the
Hereafter their hearts are denied
and they are arrogant
okay your God is one God
but those who do not believe in the
Hereafter will set up other gods beside
God that's what it means
you serious
you you people are fortunate most of you
were born in a non-muslim house
and and they uh
they will get double 31. this will be
another problem
you get twice as much as as me
the person who grew up in a Muslim house
the Quran says that those who grew up in
a non-muslim house and they became
Muslim and accepted the Quran as their
book they can stop at the reward
so I grew up in a Muslim house my
parents say if you're a good person you
have to be a Muslim you must believe in
God
you must be a Muslim you must believe in
God and so forth so I grew up saying I'm
a Muslim I believe in God I'm a Muslim I
believe in God you know because my
parents taught me so but
here is arrested after death
you know they really don't believe it
you just say it because the third taught
them to say that
foreign
how do we distinguish
this is the verse that that I wanted to
share next that those who do not believe
in the Hereafter I will God saw them on
the day of judgment that they did not
that their hearts were denied
by this Criterion here when you tell
them the Quran alone they run
this is the criteria
this is the sign that will teach them on
the day of judgment that they were
saying with their mouth I'm a Muslim
but their hearts inside were denied and
they didn't know it
so this is the starting
the another verse about those who do not
believe in the Hereafter is in Surah 6
verse 112.
612 show us the Hadith and Sundar test
where people do not believe God when he
says the Quran is complete and purpose
foreign
who invent and narrate to each other
fancy words
in order to deceive
have you Lord will not have done it you
shall disregard them and their
inventions
this is God's way in order that the
minds of us who do not really believe in
the Hereafter see it's the same
expression
because red heart inside
are denied
and we see that but I feel that
consistently those who do not believe in
the here after consistently
they will they will run away from the
Quran and all you know they attracted to
the Fabrications against the prophet but
before Hadith Sunda
and this will show them on the day of
judgment that their hearts were denied
that they they were not satisfied with
the word of God
alone
39 45.
thank you
line fortified as the great Criterion
that tells you
if you or anyone you're speaking with
talking to
is really a Believer or a false believer
it says when God Alone is advocated the
hearts of those who do not believe in
the Hereafter rain could ever see but
when Idols are mentioned
besides him they Rejoice they become
happy when you speak about Allah alone
they don't like them
the same expressed
they don't like it you have to mention
besides God Mary or Jesus or Muhammad or
Ali or somebody
you cannot speak about Allah alone to
them they will not be had but when you
mention someone else they'll be happy so
this is a sign that they do not believe
in the here
that's the sign the great criteria for
you me anyone you talk to
and this is why I have it at the
beginning of the first day
because it is the great criteria to tell
you exactly if your heart is denying or
not if you are a Muslim or you're
deceiving yourself you tell yourself I'm
a Muslim when you read more
these are the signs
finally
just look up the same Surah 39 verse 65.
Prophet Muhammad
is our example
and his example is to uphold the Quran
though to run nothing but the Quran
and here is
a statement directors to the prophet
says it has been redeemed to you
Muhammad and to those before you that if
you ever fall into I would worship
all the works will be modified and you
will be a loser
after all the work he did after all the
suffering he went through
after being banished from his hometown
if you ever fed an idol worship all his
Works would have been nullified
doesn't matter what a nice guy you are
doesn't it doesn't doesn't matter how
nice you are how honest and truthful
and beloved and benevited and charitable
doesn't matter if you if you idolize
anyone or anything all your work is in
pain
because we exist in this world to
worship Allah alone this is the whole
idea
because Satan wanted to be a god with
God
so God created us to show Satan and to
show the angels that we will worship god
without putting anything besides him to
put Muhammad next to Allah or Jesus next
to Allah or maybe next to Allah then
you'll prove Satan's point
we prove that God needs apartment God
needs Muhammad in order to be worshiped
or God needs Jesus to be worshiped
because God needs Moses or Mary or some
something be worth it we are here to
prove that God can will be worshiped
alone without anything with him this is
the whole idea of the Quran
this is the that's why it is the only
unforgivable offense
another finally can I just remember
another word
verse 10 we're going to start at 10 40
10. I'm gonna close with this I promise
at the bottom of the page three Twenty
One HD 21 at the bottom it says worship
God Alone
it says those who disbelieved would be
thought on the day of judgment God's
abhorrence towards you is even greater
than your opponents towards yourself
because you were invited to believe but
you chose to just believe
11 says they will say our Lord you have
given us two debts and two lives we now
confess our sins is there any way out
that is out of here
the answer in 12 says this is because
when when invited to worship God alone
you disbelieve but when items were
mentioned besides him you believe
Allah gentleman has been decreed by God
the most exhausted the grave
foreign
so powerful activity
but that's that's the wrong concept of
everyone's sins
because
let's listen to these questions and
answer maybe when God wants us to
benefit
from
the the concept that we all said we do
go through stances
where where we do not
uh follow the commands exactly you can't
be centered
but hopefully before you die you can
read states where you are you are
absolutely selfless you don't have any
sense of the past
right now now it is in your hand to
commit to sin or not as of this moment
now if you fall himself by due to
ignorance
and when you repent you know what to do
but it is absolutely in your hand to
follow the Quran exactly to the left
does this make sense
we do not have to be a sinner
it is not true that we are all sinners
you can get rid of all your sin and you
and you will therefore from that timer
you have a perfect life is What God Says
you have a perfect life absolutely no
problem
no traffic tickets no headaches no
stomachache no sickness you guarantee it
absolutely guarantee helps with peace of
mind perfect habit
to some glasses in the Quran Surah 24
55.
and you've got some pretty well God
promises there
someone wanted to come to your hand and
you get scared you're not to watch it
you certainly I mean I'm giving you an
explain
because that God will not
put anything to start doing that to die
at that moment there is nothing anyone
in the whole world can do about it
because the method inside of your death
is already written down
and you cannot die except it was a
personal decree from God personal degree
God must sign your death certificate
therefore a person comes with a gun can
do nothing to you
because they have to sign the
certificate of your death from God
himself personally
that no one knows when you will die no
one this is the Angels everyone not even
the answer to God
also comes from Allah
yes he said earlier that uh they would
receive the double reward right for
comparing his Muslims and the state
before that everybody has the same test
so I don't you know
architecture because then you get a
double reward they're passing the same
commission no they have to they have
additional purpose but we have to to
trust because the parents told them
Jesus God is the Son of God
this kind of thing and they have to
overcome this
to Messiah you know God wants to be
generous with them there's nothing
anyone can do so that's what God says
God says that if you if you grow up
under Muslim circumstances
foreign
thank you
the end for example at the end of Surah
57.
and they also going to end the third
party I would give up on the subject
congratulations
foreign
what was it
this is Christmas Eve and it seems but I
thought the people that have a family
reunions
the football in the city
YouTube has it yeah
this Merry Christmas from here
it's 21.
here as a commandment
you can't complete the hatch a number of
observers for God
if you are preventive then offer a
sacrifice and do not resume prepping
your hair until your offer has reached
it's destination
if you are in or suffering
some hit injury then you may cut your
hair and exit for years by fasting so
we're giving Authority for some other
form of water
during the Roman times of Peace you
break the state of sanctity between
Umbra and height
when X player by offering the sacrifice
in the past three days till it touched
on seven days
77 23rd floor
was completely intense provided we do
not live at the circuit mosque he said
represent God and know that God
restricting and forcing Justice
okay all the sound complicated but it
has to do with the have ritual
when you go perhaps
we will struck out by the Umbra
sometimes you have to do foreign
runs between
the remote the software model of 75
that completely wrong let me go into
time
so if you decide to break the
state of abroad
between
Omron has said as soon as you enter into
that state of sanctity you don't do any
vanity do not make up your face you
don't cut your hair
it's a
it's a it's another form of making the
body useless to telling your body I'm
not going to beautify you and
thank you
look pretty or anything after this
happens all people don't share the men
don't share
you don't cut it here
you can shower and everything
um but we don't work most the
distinguish but it's been before
you are very Central Florida you see it
for the men that just perceived
so it had people going and you cannot
tell rooms listen was poor
and they all look translated
so all the practice Minister are here
props built the boss over your body
you have
Brothers okay
so let me go through this sentence by
sentence now these are complete they had
some other observance from God so this
is something you have to do as soon as
whenever you can
plan on it and when you can that will
make you able to along with what I'm
doing
of course the first person to announce
had towards everyone
and this is
22 I think this is verse 27.
right now